<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mores on Eric Ngigi</title>
    <link>/more/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mores on Eric Ngigi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/more/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Elevator Pitch</title>
      <link>/more/pitch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/more/pitch/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Are you seeking an accomplished AWS Cloud Engineer with a proven track record of over 3 years in the industry, coupled with extensive Linux expertise? Look no further. With a deep understanding of cloud architecture and hands-on experience with AWS services, I bring a unique blend of technical skill and real-world problem-solving. My proficiency in designing, deploying, and optimizing cloud solutions, combined with a mastery of Linux systems, empowers me to create scalable and reliable infrastructures. Whether it&amp;rsquo;s crafting seamless migrations, implementing robust security measures, or ensuring high availability, I am poised to drive innovation and efficiency in your cloud environment. Elevate your cloud capabilities with an AWS Cloud Engineer who bridges strategic vision with actionable results.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>/more/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/more/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;about-me&#34;&gt;About Me&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am a dedicated Linux enthusiast and advocate of open-source software, possessing extensive experience in the development and maintenance of Linux systems. My professional journey spans years of cultivating a profound comprehension of the intricate mechanics of the Linux kernel, coupled with a comprehensive mastery of diverse Linux distributions, encompassing Arch Linux, Debian, Ubuntu, and CentOS.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, I possess proficient skills in an array of programming languages such as Python, Go, JAMstack, and Bash scripting. My adeptness in these languages has been instrumental in orchestrating automation and optimizing processes throughout my tenure in the DevOps domain. This proficiency in automation, intertwined with my prowess in infrastructure as code, has been pivotal in enhancing system performance, curtailing downtime, and fostering scalability.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My advocacy for free software underscores my unwavering belief in the transformative potential of open-source software, catalyzing empowerment for individuals and enterprises alike. I am steadfast in my commitment to disseminating knowledge and advancing the cause of free software whenever feasible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Should you seek a Linux specialist whose fervor for free software is complemented by a reservoir of technical competencies, your search concludes here. Together, we can craft tailor-made solutions to address your organizational requirements with efficacy. For an in-depth overview of my professional trajectory, please refer to my &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/erik-ngigi&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; &gt;LinkedIn&lt;/a&gt;
 profile. You can also access my comprehensive &lt;a href=&#34;/documents/Curriculum-Vitae.pdf&#34; &gt;resume&lt;/a&gt;
 for a detailed professional background.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I maintain a blog focused primarily on my exploits in software development and DevOps. This platform is replete with an array of how-to guides, tutorials, and insights drawn from my personal project undertakings. If you wish to initiate contact, please direct your emails to &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:ericmosesngigi@gmail.com&#34; &gt;ericmosesngigi@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;professional-it-certification&#34;&gt;Professional IT Certification&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AWS Cloud Practitioner&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;(Ongoing)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Expected Completion Date:&lt;/em&gt; September 2023&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; This certification from Amazon Web Services (AWS) validates my understanding of cloud concepts, AWS services, and the basics of cloud computing. It demonstrates my commitment to staying up-to-date with the latest cloud technologies and my ability to leverage AWS services to design and deploy scalable solutions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CompTIA A+&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Date of Completion:&lt;/em&gt; June 2022&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; This certification covers essential IT operational roles and technical support. It verifies my knowledge in areas such as hardware, networking, mobile devices, operating systems, and security. With CompTIA A+, I have demonstrated competence in maintaining and troubleshooting various devices and systems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Microsoft Certified: Azure Fundamentals&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Date of Completion:&lt;/em&gt; August 2021&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; This certification confirms my foundational knowledge of Microsoft Azure cloud services. It showcases my understanding of Azure services, cloud concepts, Azure pricing, SLA, and lifecycle, empowering me to work effectively with Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s cloud platform.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Certified Information Systems Security Professional (CISSP)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Date of Completion:&lt;/em&gt; December 2020&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; CISSP is a globally recognized certification in the field of information security. It validates my expertise in designing, implementing, and managing security programs and practices. This certification underscores my commitment to ensuring robust security measures across IT systems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Oracle Linux OCA&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Date of Completion:&lt;/em&gt; July 2020&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt; The Oracle Linux OCA certification demonstrates my proficiency in working with Oracle Linux systems. It validates my ability to perform essential administrative tasks such as installation, configuration, and troubleshooting. This certification highlights my expertise in Linux-based environments and my dedication to optimizing system performance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These certifications collectively showcase my commitment to professional development and my diverse skill set in various areas of IT, including cloud computing, security, and Linux administration. As technology continues to evolve, I am enthusiastic about expanding my knowledge and contributing to innovative solutions in the IT industry.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Journey as an AWS Cloud Engineer</title>
      <link>/more/portfolio/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/more/portfolio/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;crowdsourced-angel-investor-marketplace---webctr-project&#34;&gt;Crowdsourced Angel Investor Marketplace - WebCTR Project&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the Crowdsourced Angel Investor Marketplace project! This initiative aims to create a dynamic and user-friendly website that serves as a platform for connecting potential angel investors with exciting startup opportunities. The project leverages the power of WebCTR to host interactive sessions that facilitate seamless communication between users.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;project-overview&#34;&gt;Project Overview&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the fast-paced world of startups, funding is often a critical factor in bringing innovative ideas to life. This project addresses this need by providing a centralized platform where startup founders can present their ideas, business plans, and pitches to a pool of potential angel investors. Similarly, investors can discover promising ventures and engage in real-time discussions with entrepreneurs through the WebCTR platform.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;key-features&#34;&gt;Key Features&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;User Profiles:&lt;/strong&gt; Both startup founders and angel investors can create personalized profiles, showcasing their expertise, interests, and past experiences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project Listings:&lt;/strong&gt; Entrepreneurs can list their startup ideas, along with detailed descriptions, financial projections, and investment requirements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Investor Search:&lt;/strong&gt; Angel investors can browse through the projects listed on the platform, filtering based on industry, investment size, and other relevant criteria.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Real-time Communication:&lt;/strong&gt; WebCTR integration enables interactive and secure communication between startup founders and potential investors through video sessions, chats, and document sharing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rating and Reviews:&lt;/strong&gt; Users can provide feedback and ratings for each other based on their interactions, enhancing trust and credibility within the platform.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Secure Payments:&lt;/strong&gt; The platform supports secure payment gateways for processing investments and funding transactions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;technologies-used&#34;&gt;Technologies Used&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Frontend:&lt;/strong&gt; The user interface is developed using modern web technologies such as HTML5, CSS3, and JavaScript frameworks like React.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Backend:&lt;/strong&gt; The server-side logic is implemented using Node.js, Express, and a relational database for efficient data management.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WebCTR:&lt;/strong&gt; WebRTC (Web Real-Time Communication) is integrated to facilitate real-time video sessions, chat, and document sharing between users.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Payment Gateways:&lt;/strong&gt; Secure payment processing is ensured through integration with popular payment gateways, providing a smooth transaction experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you for your interest in the Crowdsourced Angel Investor Marketplace project. We&amp;rsquo;re excited to bring together visionary entrepreneurs and passionate investors on a single platform. Let&amp;rsquo;s collaborate and drive innovation together!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can view the group slides by clicking on the link: &lt;a href=&#34;/documents/milestone10_group_work.pdf&#34; &gt;Group Work Document&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Watch the video and explore the tangible results of our hard work and dedication.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/y4mvNF_Z6JA&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;inventory-management-and-automated-tax-returns-system-with-crater-invoicing&#34;&gt;Inventory Management and Automated Tax Returns System with Crater Invoicing&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the Inventory Management and Automated Tax Returns System project, powered by Crater Invoicing! This project combines the robust features of Crater Invoicing, an open-source invoicing application, with advanced functionalities to streamline inventory management and automate tax return processes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;project-overview-1&#34;&gt;Project Overview&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In today&amp;rsquo;s competitive business landscape, efficient inventory management and accurate tax reporting are essential for sustainable growth. This project tackles these challenges by leveraging the power of Crater Invoicing to create a comprehensive system that not only handles invoicing but also seamlessly integrates inventory management and automated tax returns.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;key-features-1&#34;&gt;Key Features&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Inventory Tracking:&lt;/strong&gt; The system enables businesses to manage their inventory in real-time. You can easily add, update, and track items, ensuring optimal stock levels and minimizing shortages or overstock situations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Automated Tax Calculation:&lt;/strong&gt; The system utilizes up-to-date tax regulations to automatically calculate taxes for each transaction. This ensures accurate tax reporting and reduces the risk of errors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tax Returns Automation:&lt;/strong&gt; The system automates the process of generating tax reports based on transaction data. This feature saves time and effort, enabling businesses to focus on core activities rather than manual tax calculations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Seamless Integration:&lt;/strong&gt; Crater Invoicing&amp;rsquo;s user-friendly interface seamlessly incorporates the inventory management and tax automation features, making it easy for users to access all functionalities from a single platform.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Customizable Reporting:&lt;/strong&gt; Generate comprehensive reports on inventory levels, transactions, and tax calculations. These reports provide insights into business operations and facilitate informed decision-making.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;technologies-used-1&#34;&gt;Technologies Used&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Crater Invoicing:&lt;/strong&gt; The core application is based on Crater Invoicing, an open-source invoicing and billing solution built using Laravel and Vue.js.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Database:&lt;/strong&gt; The system uses a relational database to store inventory data, transactions, and tax-related information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Automated Tax Engine:&lt;/strong&gt; A custom automated tax engine is developed, incorporating tax regulations and rules to accurately calculate taxes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reporting Framework:&lt;/strong&gt; Custom reporting modules are implemented to generate insightful reports on inventory, transactions, and tax-related data.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;getting-started&#34;&gt;Getting Started&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Clone the Crater Invoicing repository: &lt;code&gt;git clone https://github.com/bytefury/crater.git&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Set up Crater Invoicing following the installation instructions provided in the repository.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Extend Crater Invoicing functionalities to include inventory management and automated tax returns. Refer to the documentation for guidance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Configure the tax engine by integrating tax rules and regulations applicable to your region.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Develop or integrate reporting modules to generate inventory and tax-related reports.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Test the system thoroughly to ensure accurate tax calculations and seamless inventory management.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;contributing&#34;&gt;Contributing&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Contributions to this project are encouraged! If you have suggestions, improvements, or bug fixes, please submit them as issues or pull requests to this repository.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;contact&#34;&gt;Contact&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For inquiries or further information, please contact our team at &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:info@inventorytaxsystem.com&#34; &gt;info@inventorytaxsystem.com&lt;/a&gt;
.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you for your interest in the Inventory Management and Automated Tax Returns System project. With Crater Invoicing as the foundation, we&amp;rsquo;re excited to provide businesses with a comprehensive solution to enhance their inventory management and automate tax reporting processes. Let&amp;rsquo;s streamline operations and boost efficiency together!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum Vitae and Cover Letters</title>
      <link>/more/templates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/more/templates/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to our diverse gallery of customizable templates. We offer a wide range of designs catering to various industries and professions. From elegant and modern to creative and artistic, our collection ensures that clients can find the perfect match for their needs. Simply select your preferred template and tailor it to showcase your unique skills and experience. Get ready to impress employers and stand out from the crowd with a professionally crafted CV and cover letter. Your dream job awaits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;resume-templates&#34;&gt;Resume Templates&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;link rel=&#34;stylesheet&#34; href=&#34;/css/hugo-easy-gallery.css&#34; /&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;gallery caption-position-none caption-effect-fade hover-effect-zoom hover-transition&#34; itemscope itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageGallery&#34;&gt;
				&lt;div class=&#34;box&#34;&gt;
				  &lt;figure itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34; itemscope itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&gt;
				    &lt;div class=&#34;img&#34; style=&#34;background-image: url(&#39;images/post/academia/resumes/Curriculum-Vitae-Templates-01.png&#39;);&#34; &gt;
				      &lt;img itemprop=&#34;thumbnail&#34; src=&#34;images/post/academia/resumes/Curriculum-Vitae-Templates-01.png&#34; alt=&#34;Curriculum Vitae Templates 01&#34; /&gt;
				    &lt;/div&gt;
			      &lt;figcaption&gt;
		          &lt;p&gt;Curriculum Vitae Templates 01&lt;/p&gt;
			      &lt;/figcaption&gt;
				    &lt;a href=&#34;images/post/academia/resumes/Curriculum-Vitae-Templates-01.png&#34; itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
				  &lt;/figure&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;div class=&#34;box&#34;&gt;
				  &lt;figure itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34; itemscope itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&gt;
				    &lt;div class=&#34;img&#34; style=&#34;background-image: url(&#39;images/post/academia/resumes/Curriculum-Vitae-Templates-02.png&#39;);&#34; &gt;
				      &lt;img itemprop=&#34;thumbnail&#34; src=&#34;images/post/academia/resumes/Curriculum-Vitae-Templates-02.png&#34; alt=&#34;Curriculum Vitae Templates 02&#34; /&gt;
				    &lt;/div&gt;
			      &lt;figcaption&gt;
		          &lt;p&gt;Curriculum Vitae Templates 02&lt;/p&gt;
			      &lt;/figcaption&gt;
				    &lt;a href=&#34;images/post/academia/resumes/Curriculum-Vitae-Templates-02.png&#34; itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
				  &lt;/figure&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;div class=&#34;box&#34;&gt;
				  &lt;figure itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34; itemscope itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&gt;
				    &lt;div class=&#34;img&#34; style=&#34;background-image: url(&#39;images/post/academia/resumes/Curriculum-Vitae-Templates-03.png&#39;);&#34; &gt;
				      &lt;img itemprop=&#34;thumbnail&#34; src=&#34;images/post/academia/resumes/Curriculum-Vitae-Templates-03.png&#34; alt=&#34;Curriculum Vitae Templates 03&#34; /&gt;
				    &lt;/div&gt;
			      &lt;figcaption&gt;
		          &lt;p&gt;Curriculum Vitae Templates 03&lt;/p&gt;
			      &lt;/figcaption&gt;
				    &lt;a href=&#34;images/post/academia/resumes/Curriculum-Vitae-Templates-03.png&#34; itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
				  &lt;/figure&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;div class=&#34;box&#34;&gt;
				  &lt;figure itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34; itemscope itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&gt;
				    &lt;div class=&#34;img&#34; style=&#34;background-image: url(&#39;images/post/academia/resumes/Curriculum-Vitae-Templates-04.png&#39;);&#34; &gt;
				      &lt;img itemprop=&#34;thumbnail&#34; src=&#34;images/post/academia/resumes/Curriculum-Vitae-Templates-04.png&#34; alt=&#34;Curriculum Vitae Templates 04&#34; /&gt;
				    &lt;/div&gt;
			      &lt;figcaption&gt;
		          &lt;p&gt;Curriculum Vitae Templates 04&lt;/p&gt;
			      &lt;/figcaption&gt;
				    &lt;a href=&#34;images/post/academia/resumes/Curriculum-Vitae-Templates-04.png&#34; itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
				  &lt;/figure&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;div class=&#34;box&#34;&gt;
				  &lt;figure itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34; itemscope itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&gt;
				    &lt;div class=&#34;img&#34; style=&#34;background-image: url(&#39;images/post/academia/resumes/Curriculum-Vitae-Templates-05.png&#39;);&#34; &gt;
				      &lt;img itemprop=&#34;thumbnail&#34; src=&#34;images/post/academia/resumes/Curriculum-Vitae-Templates-05.png&#34; alt=&#34;Curriculum Vitae Templates 05&#34; /&gt;
				    &lt;/div&gt;
			      &lt;figcaption&gt;
		          &lt;p&gt;Curriculum Vitae Templates 05&lt;/p&gt;
			      &lt;/figcaption&gt;
				    &lt;a href=&#34;images/post/academia/resumes/Curriculum-Vitae-Templates-05.png&#34; itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
				  &lt;/figure&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;div class=&#34;box&#34;&gt;
				  &lt;figure itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34; itemscope itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&gt;
				    &lt;div class=&#34;img&#34; style=&#34;background-image: url(&#39;images/post/academia/resumes/Curriculum-Vitae-Templates-06.png&#39;);&#34; &gt;
				      &lt;img itemprop=&#34;thumbnail&#34; src=&#34;images/post/academia/resumes/Curriculum-Vitae-Templates-06.png&#34; alt=&#34;Curriculum Vitae Templates 06&#34; /&gt;
				    &lt;/div&gt;
			      &lt;figcaption&gt;
		          &lt;p&gt;Curriculum Vitae Templates 06&lt;/p&gt;
			      &lt;/figcaption&gt;
				    &lt;a href=&#34;images/post/academia/resumes/Curriculum-Vitae-Templates-06.png&#34; itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
				  &lt;/figure&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;div class=&#34;box&#34;&gt;
				  &lt;figure itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34; itemscope itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&gt;
				    &lt;div class=&#34;img&#34; style=&#34;background-image: url(&#39;images/post/academia/resumes/Curriculum-Vitae-Templates-07.png&#39;);&#34; &gt;
				      &lt;img itemprop=&#34;thumbnail&#34; src=&#34;images/post/academia/resumes/Curriculum-Vitae-Templates-07.png&#34; alt=&#34;Curriculum Vitae Templates 07&#34; /&gt;
				    &lt;/div&gt;
			      &lt;figcaption&gt;
		          &lt;p&gt;Curriculum Vitae Templates 07&lt;/p&gt;
			      &lt;/figcaption&gt;
				    &lt;a href=&#34;images/post/academia/resumes/Curriculum-Vitae-Templates-07.png&#34; itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
				  &lt;/figure&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;div class=&#34;box&#34;&gt;
				  &lt;figure itemprop=&#34;associatedMedia&#34; itemscope itemtype=&#34;http://schema.org/ImageObject&#34;&gt;
				    &lt;div class=&#34;img&#34; style=&#34;background-image: url(&#39;images/post/academia/resumes/Curriculum-Vitae-Templates-08.png&#39;);&#34; &gt;
				      &lt;img itemprop=&#34;thumbnail&#34; src=&#34;images/post/academia/resumes/Curriculum-Vitae-Templates-08.png&#34; alt=&#34;Curriculum Vitae Templates 08&#34; /&gt;
				    &lt;/div&gt;
			      &lt;figcaption&gt;
		          &lt;p&gt;Curriculum Vitae Templates 08&lt;/p&gt;
			      &lt;/figcaption&gt;
				    &lt;a href=&#34;images/post/academia/resumes/Curriculum-Vitae-Templates-08.png&#34; itemprop=&#34;contentUrl&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
				  &lt;/figure&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
 
 
 
 
   
 
 
 &lt;script src=&#34;https://code.jquery.com/jquery-1.12.4.min.js&#34; integrity=&#34;sha256-ZosEbRLbNQzLpnKIkEdrPv7lOy9C27hHQ+Xp8a4MxAQ=&#34; crossorigin=&#34;anonymous&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
 &lt;script src=&#34;/js/load-photoswipe.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
 
 
 &lt;link rel=&#34;stylesheet&#34; href=&#34;https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/photoswipe/4.1.1/photoswipe.min.css&#34; integrity=&#34;sha256-sCl5PUOGMLfFYctzDW3MtRib0ctyUvI9Qsmq2wXOeBY=&#34; crossorigin=&#34;anonymous&#34; /&gt;
 &lt;link rel=&#34;stylesheet&#34; href=&#34;https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/photoswipe/4.1.1/default-skin/default-skin.min.css&#34; integrity=&#34;sha256-BFeI1V+Vh1Rk37wswuOYn5lsTcaU96hGaI7OUVCLjPc=&#34; crossorigin=&#34;anonymous&#34; /&gt;
 &lt;script src=&#34;https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/photoswipe/4.1.1/photoswipe.min.js&#34; integrity=&#34;sha256-UplRCs9v4KXVJvVY+p+RSo5Q4ilAUXh7kpjyIP5odyc=&#34; crossorigin=&#34;anonymous&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
 &lt;script src=&#34;https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/photoswipe/4.1.1/photoswipe-ui-default.min.js&#34; integrity=&#34;sha256-PWHOlUzc96pMc8ThwRIXPn8yH4NOLu42RQ0b9SpnpFk=&#34; crossorigin=&#34;anonymous&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
 
 
 &lt;div class=&#34;pswp&#34; tabindex=&#34;-1&#34; role=&#34;dialog&#34; aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34;&gt;
 
 &lt;div class=&#34;pswp__bg&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
 
 &lt;div class=&#34;pswp__scroll-wrap&#34;&gt;
     
     &lt;div class=&#34;pswp__container&#34;&gt;
       &lt;div class=&#34;pswp__item&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
       &lt;div class=&#34;pswp__item&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
       &lt;div class=&#34;pswp__item&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;
     
     &lt;div class=&#34;pswp__ui pswp__ui--hidden&#34;&gt;
     &lt;div class=&#34;pswp__top-bar&#34;&gt;
       
       &lt;div class=&#34;pswp__counter&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
       &lt;button class=&#34;pswp__button pswp__button--close&#34; title=&#34;Close (Esc)&#34;&gt;&lt;/button&gt;
       &lt;button class=&#34;pswp__button pswp__button--share&#34; title=&#34;Share&#34;&gt;&lt;/button&gt;
       &lt;button class=&#34;pswp__button pswp__button--fs&#34; title=&#34;Toggle fullscreen&#34;&gt;&lt;/button&gt;
       &lt;button class=&#34;pswp__button pswp__button--zoom&#34; title=&#34;Zoom in/out&#34;&gt;&lt;/button&gt;
       
       
       &lt;div class=&#34;pswp__preloader&#34;&gt;
         &lt;div class=&#34;pswp__preloader__icn&#34;&gt;
           &lt;div class=&#34;pswp__preloader__cut&#34;&gt;
             &lt;div class=&#34;pswp__preloader__donut&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
           &lt;/div&gt;
         &lt;/div&gt;
       &lt;/div&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;
     &lt;div class=&#34;pswp__share-modal pswp__share-modal--hidden pswp__single-tap&#34;&gt;
       &lt;div class=&#34;pswp__share-tooltip&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;
     &lt;button class=&#34;pswp__button pswp__button--arrow--left&#34; title=&#34;Previous (arrow left)&#34;&gt;
     &lt;/button&gt;
     &lt;button class=&#34;pswp__button pswp__button--arrow--right&#34; title=&#34;Next (arrow right)&#34;&gt;
     &lt;/button&gt;
     &lt;div class=&#34;pswp__caption&#34;&gt;
       &lt;div class=&#34;pswp__caption__center&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;
     &lt;/div&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fill out the following &lt;a href=&#34;https://forms.gle/iBx1335f6F5cfSLh7&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; &gt;google forms&lt;/a&gt;
 to get a custom Curriculum Vitae&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;pricing&#34;&gt;Pricing&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Package&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;text-align:right&#34;&gt;Price (Kes)&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1 Curriculum Vitae&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:right&#34;&gt;Kes 500&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1 Curriculum Vitae, 1 Cover Letter&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:right&#34;&gt;Kes 550&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1 Curriculum Vitae, 2 Cover Letters&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:right&#34;&gt;Kes 600&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1 Curriculum Vitae, 3 Cover Letters&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:right&#34;&gt;Kes 650&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2 Curriculum Vitae&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:right&#34;&gt;Kes 600&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2 Curriculum Vitae, 1 Cover Letter&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:right&#34;&gt;Kes 650&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2 Curriculum Vitae, 2 Cover Letters&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:right&#34;&gt;Kes 700&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;2 Curriculum Vitae, 3 Cover Letters&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:right&#34;&gt;Kes 750&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;3 Curriculum Vitae&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:right&#34;&gt;Kes 800&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;3 Curriculum Vitae, 1 Cover Letter&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:right&#34;&gt;Kes 850&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;3 Curriculum Vitae, 2 Cover Letters&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:right&#34;&gt;Kes 900&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;3 Curriculum Vitae, 3 Cover Letters&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:right&#34;&gt;Kes 1000&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
